Enkhdavaa Batlkhagva



🕲 batlkhagva.e@gmail.com 😢 dave.bat.io 📢 @enkhdavaa 🛅 Enkhdavaa Batlkhagva

I have five years of experience in software development. In this period, I gained in-depth knowledge in scrum/agile, software design, digital twin, and model based testing. Moreover, I consistently improves my technical skills in the area of web and game development, and machine learning.

Experience

Software Designer

ICT Netherlands B.V.

☐ Jan 2021 — Present

Q Eindhoven, NL

- · Created an infrastructure strategy for using Model-Based-Testing at Thermo Fisher Scientific.
- Created state transition models for testing various subsystems of the TEM microscope at Thermo Fisher Scientific.
- Designed and developed 3D virtual hardware simulator for testing the control software of a factory at ICT Group.

.NET C#, Unity 3D, C++

Software Designer Trainee

Thermo Fisher Scientific

☐ Jan 2020 — Oct 2020

Q Eindhoven, NL

• Designed and developed a proof of concept for 3D virtual hardware simulator tool. The tool is for testing software using Unity3D game engine.

.NET C#, Unity 3D, Matlab

Embedded Software Engineer

Tavan Bogd Management

Mar 2018 — Sep 2018

Ulaanbaatar, MNG

- Contributed to implementing contactlesss payment using wireless technologies (Bluetooth and WIFI).
- · Created a windows desktop application for exchanged data with Oracle DB.

.NET C#, C

Embedded Software Intern

Innovation for High Performance Microelectronics LLC

□ Jan 2017 — Mar 2017

• Frankfurt (Oder), DE

• Implemented firmware drivers for a platform that measures a power consumption with high precision.

 \mathbf{C}

Embedded Software Engineer

Ametros Solutions LLC

☐ Jul 2015 — Sep 2016

Ulaanbaatar, MNG

- Developed firmware drivers for home automation devices (light-switch, intrusion and air quality sensors).
- Contributed developing wireless data transmission between devices.

.NET C#, C

Projects

Model Based Testing (MBT)

Thermo Fisher Scientific

Oct 2021 — Present

Eindhoven, NL

- · Developed state transition models for random test generation
- Created a testing workflow for development process
- · Developed adapters for CI by connecting SUT with MBT
- Created documentations and presentations for users

Axini, .NET C#, C++, GIT, Jenkins, Shell scripting

Center Of Excellence (COE)

ICT Netherlands B.V.

☐ Jan 2021 — Oct 2022

Eindhoven, NL

- Designed and developed a virtual 3D factory simulator to replace hardware testing dependency
- Developed HAL interface for the simulator (DT) for higher abstraction layer software
- Created CI & CD for the simulator (DT)

Unity3D, OPC-UA, .NET C#, GIT, Docker, Bamboo CI

Virtual Hardware Simulator for Transmission Electron Microscope (EngD)

Thermo Fisher Scientific

☐ Jan 2020 — Oct 2020

Eindhoven, NL

• Deisgned and implemented a 3D virtual hardware simulator for firmware and software testing so that testing is not dependent on real hardware.

Unity3D, .NET C#, GIT, Matlab, Docker

Dependency Management and Scope Control for HMI products (EngD)

Thermo Fisher Scientific

Sep 2019 — Dec 2019

Eindhoven, NL

Goal: Codeveloped a domain-specific language and a livecode dependency checker to detect software architechture

Role: Software engineer co-developing a live dependency checker

Roslyn, .NET C#

Designing Smart Landing System for Agricultural Drones (EngD)

AgroTech

May 2019 — Jul 2019

Eindhoven, NL

Goal: Design and implement the drone control software to save time of field analytics

Education

Engineering Doctorate (EngD) in Software Technology

Eindhoven University of Technology

Oct 2018 — Oct 2020

• Eindhoven, NL

BSc Electronics Engineering Technology

Mongolian University Of Science and Technology

☐ Aug 2011 − Jul 2015

Ulaanbaatar, MNG

Hobby

- Bouldering, Improvization, Running
- · Playing guitar, sketching
- Game development

Role: CI engineer and software engineer, responsible for proposing design choices and co-developing the drone control

Python, DroneKit

Face AI for Condition Monitoring (EngD)

Philips Healthcare

☐ Jan 2019 — Apr 2019

Eindhoven, NL

Goal: Add new features to the existing remote consultation system using AI services (Microsoft face AI, Amazon Rekognition)

Role: Software developer/Configuration manager responsible for co-developing back-end services using C# and implementing a CI pipeline

Microsoft Face AI, Amazon rekognition, .NET C#

Skills

| C# | •••• |
|---------------------------|------|
| Agile Scrum | •••• |
| Git | •••• |
| C++ | •••• |
| JavaScript and TypeScript | •••• |
| Python | •••• |